MUKUND NAGAR

FULL STACK WEB DEVELOPER

github.com/mukund1545

mkndnagar@gmail.com +91-7073604523

linkedin.com/in/mukund-nagar-83a875176

Profile Summary

Proactive Computer Science major(8.4 GPA) currently attending Anand International College Of Engineering, with 3+ months of work experience. Aiming to leverage a proven knowledge of Full Stack Web Development. Frequently praised as diligent by peers.

SkillSet

- HTML
- Express.js
- Javascript
- Java
- C/C++

- CSS
- Node.js
- Mongodb
- MYSQL

Education

Anand International College of Engg.

2019-2023

B.Tech in Computer Science & Engineering

Work Experience

Fresher

Internships

10 October 2022-10 December 2022

Rajasthan Police Crime Branch

- Helping in Implementation of RajKaj (e-file) system in Police Headquarters
- Analysis of FIR Reporting website
- Role of Business Analyst

MNJ Organic Foods Pvt Ltd.

1st Jan 2022-30th Jan 2022

- Made an E-commerce Store
- Organic Foods Store
- Used a Website builder called Digital Showroom

Bharti Sangrahita

1st Sep 2021-15th Sep 2021

- Made a blogger website
- Organization that has been working for educating needy children by providing education at just 1₹ per month
- Used Blogger.com

Projects

Tractor Dealer Website

- Made a website which might be useful as a landing page for a tractor dealer
- link for the Repository- https://mukund1545.github.io/

Software Engineering Lab Projects

- All the projects of Argouml which I have studied and implemented
- link for the Repository- https://mukund1545.github.io/

DSA Programs

- All the programs of DSA which I have studied and implemented
- link for the Repository- https://mukund1545.github.io/

Oops Programs

- All the programs of Oops Concepts which I have studied and implemented
- link for the Repository- https://mukund1545.github.io/